SERGEY RADKOV

Boise ID 83714 | 208.283.9080 | radkovsn@gmail.com

http://sergeyradkov.github.io www.linkedin.com/in/radkovsn https://github.com/sergeyradkov

Permanent Work Authorization No Visa Sponsorship Required Open to Relocation

TECHNOLOGIES

Proficiencies

HTML / CSS Node.js
JavaScript NPM
Bootstrap Bower
Angular.js GitHub
jQuery Heroku

API's Visual Studio Code

Facebook Messenger

Have experience with

Foundation MVC Pattern

Twilio Java Firebase C#

JSData IntelliJ IDEA

MySQL

PROJECTS

Messenger Bot for Better Business Bureau

Facebook Messenger Bot is the back-end application for Better Business Bureau to find appropriate businesses through Facebook Messenger. In this project are used Node JS as back-end, BBB API (to look for find trustworthy businesses in North America), Google Maps API(to identify user location), the huge dictionary of US states/cities and Facebook Messenger Platform.

https://m.me/BBBSnakeRiverRegion

Quickbooks Helper Web Application

Self-Service customer updater tool. Allows a customer to enter their phone information and verify that they are a customer, and then allows the customer edit their name, address, and email information. This information is then updated into QuickBooks(tm) using the QuickBooks(tm) SDK.

https://gbemailgrabber.herokuapp.com

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Junior Web Developer with a passion for online businesses has extensive knowledge of business analysis and substantial experience creating logical and innovative solutions to complex problems to increase efficiency, with 5+ years' telematics service promotion and 8 years' management experience.

EDUCATION

Web Development Immersive Full Stack Course

BoiseCodeWorks | Boise, Idaho | 04/2016 – 06/2016 The leading premier coding bootcamp in Idaho.

Master's Degree | Transport Management

(combined bachelor/master program)

State University of Management | Moscow, Russia | 1997 – 2002 Russia's leading university in the field of management education

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Web Developer

freelance | Boise, Idaho | 2016 - now

Created and maintained web pages using HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, AngularJS and Node.js, optimized web pages for mobile, and debugged for better code, updated existing code and learned new technologies on the fly.

Senior Product Engineer

Volvo Truck Russia | Moscow, Russia | 2010 -2015 A branch of Volvo Trucks, a global truck manufacturer.

Promoted Volvo telematics services, provided technical support for 600+ customers and 100+ team members, established new consulting service using Volvo's telematics.

Transportation Coordinator

TOTAL E&P Russia | Moscow, Russia | 2008 - 2010 Subsidiary of TOTAL S.A., a multinational oil and gas company.

Transportation Manager

Unimilk | Moscow, Russia | 2006 - 2007 Russia's largest dairy producer; now owned by Danone.

Transportation Specialist

PKD Optima | Moscow, Russia | 2003-2006 General distributor of Philip Morris USA in Russia

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

- Practical problem solver with exceptional attention to detail
- Strong presentation, communication and negotiation skills
- Demonstrated success in project and staff management
- Ability to adapt to rapidly changing environments
- International experience and bi-lingual in English and Russian